(How to make enchanted knife.)
Some matters you have to solve it yourself.
Can't rely on anyone.
No matter how far we run. He will find us.
That Gott. He's like bad karma.
Following us everywhere.
But the karma itself...
it happens to involve the Satra Sutra book.
Trust me, and you'll survive.
Bring me betel leaves and uncooked rice.
You bastard, Anon!
You animal!
You bastard!
Help!
Come quickly!
Hey! Anyone outside, come look quickly!
- Hurry!
- Hey, sir!
Sir! Sir!
This town will be mine.
All mine.
No more running. Better to just fight.
Let's settle this.
I'll have Mom stay with Auntie
in Lampoon for a while.
But in all my life,
I've never seen anyone practice
black magic with such power.
There was one time
when he was hit with incense ash.
Did you see his face?
Gott's face changed.
It was like someone else
was inside his body.
Or maybe it's not human.
It's not human, man.
Oh, Uncle.
But it's a consciousness
that refuses to be reborn.
It lingers, obsessed with revenge.
Trapped by the karma
it creates in every life.
The reason it can inhabit a human body...
is because it steals other people's bodies.
After a long time,
it consumes them and makes it its own body.
That's why they call it
a 'possessing spirit.'
Oh, and what does it want, Uncle?
It's vicious. That means it wants revenge.
It wants immortality.
Lingering until it becomes a demon.
That's what.
And what does that have to do
with the human-skin Satra Sutra book?
This Satra Sutra book...
If it can open that book,
it won't just become immortal.
It will also be able to
control the evil spirits
that are contained within that book.
I don't think that's good news at all.
And will there be no one
who can subdue it, Uncle?
There is one.
Or maybe it's you guys.
Aren't you quite something? Huh?
Killing people and living a normal life.
Truly, purely evil.
You're thick with defilements.
Greed.
Desire.
Stupidity.
What's the plan now, you wicked man?
- I will run for MP.
- Hmm.
And I will become an MP.
Hmm.
Don't forget, here, money can buy anything.
I told you.
Sometimes,
all those spells, charms, magical powers...
might not even be a match for money.
People here worship money as their god.
It can buy anything.
And honestly,
I don't have to work for anyone anymore.
Hmm.
This is humanity, huh.
Yes.
Unfearing of sin.
No reverence, no faith.
How many times do I have to
show you people?
You don't chant praises.
You question those you should revere.
Hard-hearted.
Where have the prayers gone?
Where are they?
Your life...
Is your suffering too little that
you dare declare war on me? Huh?
A man like you...
must serve me for the rest of your life.
That's it.
Thelo Moggallano.
Antaradhayitva.
Bhūmisukhumam Pramano.
Bhagavato Iddhiya.
Attano Sarire.
Mamsam.
Lohitam.
From now on,
you are the one with the Wind element
as your spiritual power.
And you...
are the one with the Water element
as your spiritual power.
The Burmese soldiers' corpses
were beheaded for ritual sacrifice.
There are no bodies of our men.
The soldiers' sword tips have no blood.
They have protective charms.
Those ghost army bastards.
The rumors are true.
That they...
have a ghost army protecting Bang Rajan.
If they use ghosts for protection,
we will use ghosts to kill them.
To a good rebirth, my friend.
I think we should hurry and
ell the people at Bang Rajan.
The Burmese know we're here now.
Mm-hmm.
I think we should have Thong...
go tell the Ban Rajan villagers.
He knows the routes well.
It's a trap.
You can't fight it.
I have to help my nephew.
As I promised to Itt.
It's karma.
Each person's karma from their past lives.
And there's really no way
to resolve karma, Uncle?
Karma, no matter how many lifetimes...
it never ends.
If the creditors of your karma
don't forgive you.
And you keep creating enmity and karma
with each other in every life...
You have to stop one of them.
To stop the karma in this lifetime.
You idiot! You should have raised your bet!
You dumbass!
There!
Right there!
Go! Go!
Whoa, hey!
Play properly! You'll do it!
Whoa! Damn it!
Damn!
I'll have Mom stay at Uncle Pong's house
in Lampoon for a while, Uncle.
As for the shop,
it's up to them.
I see they're happy.
I don't want to destroy their dreams.
And what about your life?
What are you going to do?
Your life is your own.
You're always taking care of others.
Don't you take care of yourself at all?
Singh.
I have nothing to give you.
Except this arcane knife.
That your father gave me.
Take it for self-defense.
You'll need it more than I will.
And remember, Singh...
If it tries to lure you in,
don't ever fall into dark arts.
Thanks, Uncle.
You're up to this, kid?
I am.
I was never afraid of anything.
And you're not afraid of Gott or Anon?
If they have the guts, let them come.
We've never been afraid to die anyway.
And aren't you afraid that...
something will happen to Singh?
Hey!
- What are you talking about?
- Fucker!
What were you talking about?
- You spooked me just now.
- You see me all day and still get scared?
I asked her if she wasn't
worried about Singh.
You're really nosy.
So, aren't you worried?
Hmm.
Of course I'm worried.
Ah-ha!
Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha!
There's a reaction! There's a reaction!
Face red, cheeks red like this.
Don't tell me...
our tiger...
has already managed to
devour the little deer's heart.
That must be it!
What are you saying?
I don't know.
I had this experience back in junior high.
I know, I can tell.
I knew it, that damn prick.
The tiger stayed quiet around me.
You guys snuck off and
did it already, no wonder!
I invited him to watch porn and
he didn't want to hang out with me.
Hmph.
- Huh?
- Distant.
Hey, no need to be shy.
It's a common, everyone goes through it.
It's normal.
Come on.
I've been with Singh since you were kids.
Well.
Damn.
Didn't I tell you not to follow me?
I just wanted to talk to you.
You're really stubborn, huh.
I just want to ask you...
to stop interfering with me.
I want to become an MP.
And make money in this business.
Which I can do without you.
However much money you want, just tell me.
I only ask for one thing.
Stop interfering with me.
Okay?
You...
are you negotiating with me?
No.
I'm not negotiating.
Backstabbing dog.
You're such a bastard.
A person like you...
just clutters up the world.
I...
I know where the person
you want to find is.
Tell me.
I said...
I found the person you're looking for.
I found her.
Hey, bro, I'll owe you for now, okay?
I have money for you. I won't stiff you.
Really, bro... I never stiff people.
Hey, bro, don't you remember?
I just paid you back.
It isn't that long ago!
Hey!
But last night you owe me
two hundred thousand in one go.
That's not including the old debt.
Whoa, bro!
Who knew he'd miss so badly?
He's been playing well
the whole season, bro!
When will you transfer it to me?
Uh...
How about mid-month, bro?
And bro, remember what I told you?
About meeting the shaman?
In prison, yeah?
He gave me fucking winning numbers.
This round I'll win, bro!
I'll pay you back immediately.
Hey, but don't tell anyone, bro!
Okay? I'm counting on you, bro.
You...
Just get me the money.
If not, I won't let you go.
I'll send people to beat you up every day.
Until you get the money for me.
Manchester United.
Manchester United? You shithead!
What are the numbers for this draw?
Hey!
What's the winning number this month?
Hurry up and tell me!
So I can go bet quickly
before they stop selling.
And next time you want anything, tell me.
I'll get it for you.
0 4 6.
Huh?
064? 046? What?
What?
He could have told me clearly.
Damn it.
You bastard.
No budget for a funeral.
And just bury him like this?
Pathetic as hell.
Ugh!
Go.
Come.
Hey, you bastard!
He's rotting, you animal!
And he won't let anyone else take him.
Come.
You bastard.
What the hell are you going to do with him?
You bastard!
You're doing this to me, Gott?
I'll kill you!
Let's go!
Come on!
Mom, you're going to
Uncle Pong's house, right?
Mm-hmm.
I'll finish packing
the clothes and then go.
I will go to the temple
to see the Monk Teacher for a bit.
Then I'll head straight to the shop.
When you reach Uncle Pong's house, Mom,
call and tell me, okay?
If everything is settled here,
I will call you.
Mm-hmm.
If anything happens,
just call and tell me what to do.
You have to take care of yourself too.
Go look at the altar.
Take something to protect you.
Don't just take care of others.
You have to take care of yourself too.
Mom.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I've never done a single thing
to make you proud.
Only caused you trouble and heartache.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I'm sorry.
I've been proud every day.
Just seeing you...
wanting to be a good person.
That's enough for me.
People...
can't choose how we're born.
Not everyone is born lucky.
But we can choose...
to be good people.
And I see you trying every day.
Someday, Singh...
Someday...
it will turn out good.
It will turn out good, son.
It will turn out good.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I'm sorry.
It will turn out good, son.
Fuck!
What's this?
Go.
Go kill them all.
(In Khmer)
Get out!
Get out! Get out!
Help! Help!
Help!
It won't be long, believe me.
They won't let us be for long.
If we stay here,
they'll definitely come in full force.
Both spirits and men.
You guys keep running this shop.
You and Jo can handle it.
What?
We started together.
No matter how long you're gone,
we'll wait for you, man.
I also want to know...
if it were me who left,
would anyone wait for me?
- I would wait.
- I'd wait.
Damn, this is so touching.
I'm gonna cry, you pricks.
Damn it.
Jo.
Hmph.
- I was joking.
- Fuck you!
- I'll kick you right out of the shop!
- If you left, I'd be happy.
Just go.
- Go, and stay gone.
- Big talk. You'd miss me if I were gone.
Damn mood-killer.
I know...
that you're watching over us.
It can't be anyone but you.
Just show your face once.
Singh.
I...
Can I just hug you once, man?
I'm worried about you, man.
Yeah, I know.
You think you're the only one
worried about him?
Come on.
Let me hug you too.
Argh, you're gonna kill me.
Damn, you must be a retired masseuse.
Thanks for the encouragement, man.
- Go, hide!
- Damn it!
Foon. Jo.
Are you hurt?
Damn it!
Are you okay?
Hey!
Singh!
Singh, help!
Foon!
Foon, you'll be okay, Foon.
You will get through it, Foon.
- Singh!
- What happened, Jo?
Something's happening to Foon!
I don't know!
What, Jo?
What happened, Jo?
I don't know! Suddenly she just
became like this and collapsed!
Blood is coming from her mouth!
Foon.
Jo, call an ambulance!
Stay strong, Foon.
The ambulance will be here soon.
Have you called?
Stay strong.
Singh.
I still...
I still don't want to die.
No.
You're not dying, Foon.
You have to stay with me, Foon.
I'm...
scared.
No, you're not.
I'm scared.
No, Foon.
What the hell did the hospital say?
No one is answering, damn it!
I don't know what the hell
everyone's doing.
I'm scared... of not being with you.
Stay with me, Foon!
I'll be with you, Foon.
I'm scared.
No, Foon.
I'm scared I won't be with you.
- You don't have to be scared.
I'll be with you, Foon.
You have to stay with me.
Singh, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
Of not being with you.
I still don't want to die.
No, you... you must not die, Foon.
No.
I want to be with you.
You will, Foon. You have to stay with me.
I'm scared.
I want to be with you.
Please.
I...
- I want to be with you.
- Foon.
Foon.
- Wake up, Foon!
- Foon.
Foon.
Foon, you have to wake up, Foon.
Don't die, Foon.
Foon!
Don't leave me like this, Foon! Foon!
Wake up, Foon!
Foon!
Foon, don't die.
Damn it.
Foon.
Singh.
Hey, Singh!
Foon wasn't shot.
Why is she bleeding?
Hatred... it is truly powerful.
It can make good people...
turn into demons.
A demon...
Something's in the wind.